I move differently. I think differently. My belief and my ability cannot be shaken. None of these guys have what I have.
You know my name, yeah? I'm gonna make you tell my name. I am going to break you.
You're gonna be slow. You're gonna be slow. I love it.
To me, it's a great procession.
Every federal agent I'm coming for. Tomorrow I'll take his head clean off.
I am the more content on burning the stream.
How many times can I ask you?
How many days can I go without you?
When I hear you to take part, when I hear you to take over.
People are always saying about the talk, and I talk, and I talk, and I talk.
But guess what? I back it up. I back it up.
I think there are tons of people who named Additionally,
Or You Deity.
The reed zone.
this is the beginning of the mcgregor era i don't give up i don't give a
i own this town i own rio de janeiro i'm sitting up here with my feet on the desk
what's anyone up there gonna do about it
the fire in my eye
i'm a fan of fantasy
you